In the twilight of their youth... her love gave him the courage to win.
A Warrior's Heart is a action, drama, family film directed by Mike Sears.
Unable to cope with his military father's sudden death in combat,
quick-tempered teen, Conor, starts getting into serious trouble.
During an intense lacrosse camp, his father's old friend challenges
Conor to get his life on track and become a man.
Conor Sullivan, played by Kellan Lutz.
Brooklyn Milligan, played by Ashley Greene.
Sgt. Major Duke Wayne, played by Adam Beach.
Claire Sullivan, played by Gabrielle Anwar.
Dupree, played by Chord Overstreet.
Coach David Milligan, played by William Mapother.
A Warrior's Heart is an American 2011 romantic
sports drama film directed by Michael F.
Sears and written by Martin Dugard.
It stars Kellan Lutz, Adam Beach, Gabrielle Anwar and Ashley Greene.
The film was released at the 2011 Cannes Film Festival on May 13,
2011 and in limited theaters on December 2, 2011.
The film explores themes of rebellion, sports, death
of father, coach, high school sports.
The tone is emotional and intense.